

CONTACTS



m.meinarts10@gmail.com



+447575827773 +37120009344











LANGUAGES

- Russian Native
- English C1+

SKILLS / WORKED WITH

- React
- Redux / Redux toolkit
- JS/ES6/Typescript
- Redux-Thunk, Formik
- Rest API, Axios
- Material UI, Ant-D
- Styled Components
- Storybook, Postman, **TDD**
- HTML, HTML5
- CSS, SASS
- Git, Github

MAKSS MEINARTS

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

Hello, I'm a front-end developer from Latvia who has experience in creating SPA. My main stack is React, Redux & Typescript, but I'm always keen on learning new stacks. I would like to learn Node.js or another backend framework to expand my abilities for building applications.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2021 - 2021

TODO-LIST

- Stack: Typescript, React, Redux-toolkit, Material UI
- · Description: Fully functioning CRUD SPA. This todo-list build with the FLUX architecture method and includes functionality like. 1. Input validations, 2. Different types of spinners, 3. Unit tests. 4. Authentication. You can follow the progress on the Github: repository view project

2022 - Present

CARDS APP

- Stack: Typescript, React, Redux.
- Description: Fully functioning CRUD SPA. Me and my team working on Anki alike desktop application that allows you to memorize concepts faster by creating or using created packs with cards inside of them. You can follow the progress on Github: repository view project

EDUCATION

2021 - Present

IT-INCUBATOR

Front-end developer (Typescript, React, Redux)

2018 - 2019

PROFESSIONAL COOKERY

Edinburgh College